Once again, we bring you a report from Gero, with the cooperation of YUKAI RESORT Gero Nagaraku!
I'm Tsuki Ohguro and Haruna Sakamoto from Team Jachi.
We are here at Geroji today as we were last time!
We are on an exciting school trip!
Today we are going to eat and walk around!
Yay!
You must be hungry.
It's time to eat.
It's lunch time, right now.
So we're going to eat a lot of delicious food from Gero!
Let's go
Kinkong kankong!
This next restaurant looks too good.
Seriously?
So you'll recognize it.
Is this it? What if it is?
You're right.
This brightly colored sign right here.
It looks like butter.
Butter sandwiches or grilled rice balls with homemade butter.
Or grilled rice balls with homemade butter.
Asiuris?
Asi lily?
It's a place where you can eat while you're in.
Wait a minute!
I have a friend.
A friend?
Yes, he's a cow.
We're not frogs here.
This is a cow.
We're cows.
Wow.
Hello.
Asiyu, the buttermilk cow.
This is the cow that's been watching over the store.
Hello, cow.
Nice to meet you.
Good afternoon.
I mean, hello.
I want you to say hello.
I mean hello.
I'd like to take a picture of you.
Will you take a picture with me?
Sure.
She agreed, though reluctantly.
You have a rather sullen voice, don't you?
Yes, she does.
Very... very... tannic.
I've been soaking in buttermilk for so long.
I've been soaking in buttermilk for so long, I've developed a voice like that.
Relax.
It's a low voice.
Yeah.
Hey, twintails.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's take a picture together.
That was fast.
What do you mean, you've been scouted out?
Where's your phone?
I'll get it.
Can you take my picture?
Okay, which way do you want to go?
I think it's better if we go over there.
Is that okay? Can I go next door?
Come on, come on.
He's a pretty good-looking guy.
Okay, I'll go.
It's nice to paint, isn't it?
A little bit of spring.
Okay, you ready?
Okay.
Okay? Thank you very much.
Has your voice changed since I last saw you?
Sort of.
I guess hanging out a lot changes your voice.
Okay, I'm going.
Smile, please.
Cheese.
Cheese! Cheese!
You're so cute.
Thank you.
Next time
A little something extra.
Next Trailer
Extra
extra
Thank you very much.
I'm homemade butter grilled rice balls with cheese butter.
Oh my god!Oh, man.
Oh no!
I can't believe the time has come for grilled onigiri!
Look at this... hot water...
So cute!
It's a bath tub.
It's so cute!
And...
Butter sandwiches made with homemade butter.
Too cute!
And is that a frog?
Frog shadow.
It's a frog's shadow.
So cute!
Then I'll eat it.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
I'm glad I'm already hungry.
It's really lunchtime.
Can I start with the grilled rice balls?
Wait for me, please.
Aren't the katsuomushi around here just as good as the rest?
It's like, "Oh, no, it's not.
Amazing.
The butter is so smooth.
Wow. It's totally different.
Grilled onigiri has a savory smell, right?
It has a savory smell, but it's mellow.
It's definitely because of the butter.
Yes, yes.
But it's not heavy at all.
I think it's fine, in fact, I welcome it.
In fact, it goes well with it.
I want more.
This is great.
I'll go first then.
Butter sandwiches made with homemade butter sandwiches.
Bon appétit.
Yum! How is it?
It's soft around the edges.
It's soft!
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
How's that? Is there butter? Is there butter?
Well, it's like butter all around, the cream inside is buttery too, but the cookie dough around it has a great buttery flavor, and it's crispy but soft, so it's really good with the inside.
It's homemade butter, so if you put a lot of butter in it, it tastes greasy, right?
I guess because it's homemade, it doesn't have that problem.
It's easy to eat.
After finishing this, I'm still waiting for more delicious food.
It's over there, isn't it?
That's right. That's where we're standing in line. I'd like to get in line.
I'm off.
Let's go!
Next, here's another spot that will look great.
This is Mr. Yasu Yoshima.
Mr. Yasu Yoshima.
Isn't he amazing? Look at this.
Three different kinds of seasonal dishes.
Oh my God, is this on top of the ebi-sen?
That's how nigiri is usually made, isn't it? For easy eating and walking around.
I see.
This place is a reflection. The food is also a reflection, but maybe it's a place to eat? I see it over there, but I was just wondering if it might be possible to eat there.
Wait. A different kind of cow?
No, no. No, no.
Not like hers.
Like I said, she's across the street. From Butterstan.
Yes. It's close by.
There are so many varieties.
I said next, but there was this long line.
That's right. They're all lined up.
I knew it, there are so many people.
I've been waiting for a long time.
This is it.
What? Nattoukuton?
Nattoucton?
Natto?
A pig eating natto.
A pig called Nattokuton?
I'll look into it.
Are you sure?
We're the ones sending out the message, so it's not okay to lie.
It's a lie.
Nattokton.
Nattokuton is named after the pigs that are fed natto powder and rice.
Are you eating natto?
I'm eating it.
Then, already, Athena is eating it.
Technically, it's natto powder.
I thought it might be hard to eat the stickiness of natto, so I made it into powder and gave it to her.
You're so kind. You're so kind.
Here comes the last forest.Here they are, the final forest.
From right to left: Akamai, Shimofuri, and Natto Baketon.
Wow, they are so shiny!
Brilliant!
Which one do you want to go first?
Natto Kaiton first.
No way!
Surprise!
Natto Bittong first.
Okay, let's go.
It's heavy.
It's so heavy!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
PASE
ni
me
I agree
I'm convinced.
Yes, it makes sense.
The rice is different from sushi.
Isn't it sweet?
Yeah, it's sweet.
It's super juicy and the oil is sweet, so I don't mind it.
It's super tasty.
I'm so happy.
Okay, bye.
Red meat?
Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
Let's try the shimofuri rush.
It's red.
Bon appétit.
Not at all like the nattokuton.
No, no, no, no.
But juicy.
Even the tenderness is totally different.
It was the center of the dish.
Mr. Shimoburi!
Bon appétit!
Because you can already see
The fat is coming out of the fibers.
It's so fatty!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Can you feel it?
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
delicious
Delicious.
No.
Mnh-mnh.
Oh, they're gone.
It's melted.
He left the rice.
Mnh-mnh.
Hey, where'd she go?
You three are amazing, you three are amazing, you three are amazing, you three are amazing, you three are amazing, you three are amazing, you three are amazing, you three are amazing.
Thank you so much for the delicious food...
I wonder if English can speak...
English is so delicious! Thank you... that's a terrible cow!
Oh, I see... you're talking to my face...
I gave it to Kara because she asked for it.
It's like this.
Bon appétit!
Okaka...
Hey...
Delicious!
Where is it?
delicious
Seasoned Genius
Delicious
The way to maximize the flavor of the meat is genius.
Look at this oil!
The oil, whether it's from the fattened beef or this fried chicken...
It's not heavy, not heavy at all.
It's not heavy at all
It's more like the kind of oil you want.
It's not heavy at all, but it's the kind of oil you want.
It's delicious!
And this sauce...
It's delicious.
Delicious!
I'm satisfied.Satisfaction
I could stay here forever and eat here every day.
Yup.
Double photo
Okay, here's the first one.
Don!
It's just a reflection.
It's a reflection.
Footbaths with colored buttermilk.
And there's an actual cow in there.
It's just not possible.
The food is delicious, but...
but if the view is pretty or beautiful
It doubles the taste.
It doubles the taste, and it doubles the ultimate taste, too.
Yes, I'm already excited.
I can't take it.
You can tell from the expression on my face
I'm sure you can tell.
And here's the second one.
D'oh!
Here it is!
It's too strong as a food picture.
It's not so bad on its own.
But the fact that it's so cute makes it even more appealing on instagram.
It's even more powerful on Instagram and so on.
I was surprised to know that there are still so many delicious foods that we don't know about yet.
Even in the East Sea.
That's right.
If you don't come here, you'll never know.
If you're interested, please be sure to take a look at these two!
I'm counting on you!
See you next time!
Bye-bye.
It's time for Orca News!
Yay!
I'll bring you the latest news about us.
First of all.
We, the collaboration unit of Coming Flavor Team Killer Whale
We are going to perform as "Shachifre" on May 18th in Shinjuku, Tokyo.
On May 18, we will be performing in Shinjuku, Tokyo.
It will be a one-man live performance as "Shachifre"!
that's right!
But we will also be performing our songs as both Shachi and Kamihure-chan.
You will be able to see us in various ways such as collaborations.
So please come and join us!
And we're also planning to expand as Shachifre-chan.
We are planning to open a show at HMV Sakaiminaten on April 23rd.
We are looking forward to seeing you at HMV Sakaiminaten!
We are looking forward to seeing you there!
And we are going to have a one-man live as Team Shachi!
We will be performing at Nagoya Castle on July 22nd.
Killer Whale Summer
Orca Summer has become a major summer event for us and our fans.
We will be performing at Nagoya Castle, the place where we were born, and we will be doing our best to make the event even more exciting.
I'm so fired up!
We are going to challenge the live performance with everyone's thoughts and feelings on our shoulders, so please be sure to come and see us.
Please be sure to come and see us.
That's all for now.